NKULULEKO MOKOENA

- nkululekokoena@gmail.com
- § South Africa, Brakpan
- in linkedin.com/in/nkululeko-mokoena-3b9769146

+27767393691/+27814259247

https://github.com/NkululekoMo

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A Full Stack Web Developer with a vast array of knowledge in many different front-end and back-end languages, responsive framework, database and best code practices. I have 1 year and 6 months experience. I am passionate in developing scalable web applications and working across the full stack. I'm looking to join forces with a suitable company to continue to grow my skill set while contributing to the positive outcome of making my company and myself famous in the world.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Information Technology

Richfield Graduate Institute of Technology 2015-2018 / Completed

Higher Certificate in Information Technology

Richfield Graduate Institute of Technology 2014 / Completed

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deviare

Full Stack Web Development (MEAN Stack) April 2021 – February 2022

- Creating websites and blogs using front-end and backend
- Creating scalable and dynamic websites
- Deploying solutions using MongoDB, AngularJs, ExpressJs, NodeJs
- Test applications and deploy websites to AWS, Docker

Deviare/Sumago Infotech - Full Stack Java Development (Trainee Developer)

April 2022 - Present

- Create student class management system using ReactJs
- Building E-commerce websites using Spring-Boot/AngularJs
- Using Spring Boot and Maven to build applications

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- MySQL
- MongoDB, ExpressJs, AngularJs, NodeJs (MEAN Stack),
- ReactJs
- Bootstrap
- Spring Boot, Spring & Maven
- Problem solving skills
- Team work
- Creativity
- Strategic planning
- Time management skills

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Online Quiz Test

- Build angular & typescript online test
- Each questions are timed for 60 seconds and display result immediately when done.
- Tech used: Spring boot, Angular, JavaScript, JSON

Portfolio Website

- Created portfolio website using HTML5,
 CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery
- Extras: Particle.js, Typed.js, Tilt.js, Scroll Reveal, Font Awesome, and JSON

E-commerce Shopping Cart

- Create an E-commerce shopping cart using Spring-Boot and Angular, JSON
- Add items into cart and check out items as well

Medicare E-commerce Online shop

Create medicine online shop using Angular,
 Typescript, Mongo DB, NodeJs

More project on:

https://github.com/NkululekoMo

Portfolio Link:

https://nkululekomo.github.io/MyPortfolio/